greatbuildings.com 2005-12-15

# Great Buildings Online Privacy Statement

[www.GreatBuildings.com](http://www.greatbuildings.com/gbc.html) provides public information on world architecture and design. We also cross-link extensively with the public forums at [www.DesignCommunity.com](http://www.designcommunity.com/home.html), and we recommend that children under age 13 should not post to any public forum without parental permission and supervision.   Please send us [your comments](http://www.greatbuildings.com/cgi-bin/suggestion.cgi?privacy.html) on our web site and web site policies. 

**Privacy Policy**

Artifice, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [www.GreatBuildings.com](http://www.greatbuildings.com/). 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

This site contains links to other sites. **www.GreatBuildings.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

We belong to the [24/7 Media Network](http://www.247media.com/), one of the largest advertising networks on the Internet. This network uses an outside company, AdForce, to display [ads on this site](http://www.greatbuildings.com/advertising.html). Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site itself does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site, and we do not provide AdForce with any special information including keywords, subject areas, zip codes or area codes. 

_AdForce's Use of Cookies_

AdForce uses a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. This allows us to measure and report aggregate information to advertisers such as the number of people who see their ad (reach) and the number of times people see their ad (frequency). It also allows us to deliver ads that are more relevant to you and avoid delivering the same ads too many times. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. AdForce will only store information provided voluntarily, but this information is not personally identifiable. If for some reason you would rather not take advantage of the benefits made possible with cookies, most browsers allow you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept. 

_AdForce's Use of IP Addresses_

AdForce delivers Internet advertisements for AdForce-enabled Web sites. In the process of delivering ads AdForce recognizes the URL and category of the active Web Page, information about your computer, such as the browser, operating system and IP address, and the home server from which you access the Internet. In some cases AdForce-enabled Web sites provide AdForce with information such as keywords, subject areas, zip codes or area codes. IMGIS uses this information to select advertisements that will work on your computer and are more relevant to your interests. Information regarding visitors to AdForce-enabled sites is aggregated for the purposes of reporting to advertisers, ad sales organizations and the Web sites. Information about specific visitors is not made available to any of these organizations. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Site logs are maintained in secure server areas accessible only to specially qualified technical staff. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact me directly: 

Kevin Matthews President Artifice, Inc. PO Box 1588 Eugene, OR 97440 USA [matthews@artifice.com](mailto:matthews@artifice.com%20\(Privacy%20Policy\))
